<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>app.logorrr.LogoRRR</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <name>LogoRRR</name>
    <summary>Effortless log file review and management</summary>
    <description>
        <p>LogoRRR makes it easy to review log files. With a focus on speed, usability, and powerful features, LogoRRR is designed to simplify log analysis for developers, system administrators, and anyone working with log data.</p>
        <p>Features include:</p>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Cross-Platform Compatibility:</b> Easily use on Windows, macOS, Linux.</li>
            <li><b>Drag and Drop:</b> Just drag and drop log files or directories for instant access.</li>
            <li><b>Interactive Filtering:</b> Effortlessly filter log entries to find exactly what you need.</li>
            <li><b>Multi-File Handling:</b> Manage and view multiple log files simultaneously.</li>
            <li><b>Zip File Support:</b> Directly work with zip files - no need to unpack data before analyzing.</li>
            <li><b>Advanced Search Options:</b> Utilize case-sensitive and regex searches for precise results.</li>
            <li><b>Real-Time Monitoring:</b> Stay updated with Unix tail -f like functionality for ongoing events.</li>
            <li><b>Efficiency at Your Fingertips:</b> Quick keyboard shortcuts streamline your workflow.</li>
            <li><b>Easy Export:</b> Copy your extracted data to the clipboard - to include it in emails for example.</li>
            <li><b>Remembers Settings:</b> LogoRRR smartly recalls your last files and settings on restart.</li>
        </ul>
    </description>
    <developer_name>LogoRRR Team</developer_name>
    <project_license>Apache-2.0</project_license>
    <url type="homepage">https://www.logorrr.app</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://www.logorrr.app/issues</url>
    <url type="help">https://www.logorrr.app/help</url>
    <provides>
        <desktop>app.logorrr.LogoRRR.desktop</desktop>
    </provides>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">app.logorrr.LogoRRR.desktop</launchable>
    <categories>
        <category>Utility</category>
        <category>Development</category>
        <category>System</category>
    </categories>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://www.logorrr.app/images/screenshot1.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://www.logorrr.app/images/screenshot2.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
</component>